Will you two slow down?
You're eating like
they're going to take it away from you.
I'm a growing girl.
It's such a pleasure seeing you
and seeing how well work is going.
Work's going really well, yeah.
My boss said that he wants to see my book
when it's done, which is really exciting.
Where are you at with that?
Oh, well, I've done four of the essays,
and I'm just kind of polishing them up.
And my hope is that it's going to be nine.
But, you know, it's a memoir.
So, have to live them first.
Tad, I don't want to just leave it
'til the end of dinner.
I hear that.
Hannah, your mother
and I have been talking,
and we feel that it may be time...
how can I phrase this?
Well, we see how well
you're doing at work.
And you really seem to be
figuring out what it is that you want.
But it may be time for one final push.
What is a "final push"?
We're not going to be
supporting you any longer.
You see, I wasn't going to
phrase it like that, Loreen,
-the way you phrased it.
-But I have no job.
No, you have an internship
that you say is going to turn into a job.
I don't know when.
You graduated from college two years ago.
We've been supporting you
for two years, and that's enough.
Do you know how crazy
the economy is right now?
I mean, all my friends
get help from their parents.
We are sympathetic to that.
But I'm your only child.
It's not like I'm draining
all your resources.
I mean, this feels very arbitrary.
You don't know anything
about our finances.
We're professors, Hannah. Professors.
We can't keep bankrolling
your groovy lifestyle.
My "groovy" lifestyle?
The bills add up.
We're covering your rent,
your insurance, your cell phone.
You said it was cheaper for you
if I was on the family plan.
Yeah.
May I get you more of anything?
No, she's fine.
-Delicious.
-Yeah.
This is nuts.
Ted, can you help me here?
I could be a drug addict.
Do you realize how lucky you are?
I mean, it doesn't have to be heroin,
it could be something
more insidious, like pills.
Which are legal,
and which a lot of kids do, all the time.
And then slowly,
they become totally useless.
They seem really high-functioning,
and then it just ruins them.
Okay, my friend Sophie,
her parents don't support her.
Last summer, she had two abortions
right in a row, and no one came with her.
What does that have to do with anything?
I'm just saying that
I am so close to the life that I want,
the life that you want for me,
that for you to just end that right now?
No more money.
-Starting when?
-Starting now.
We can talk about it tomorrow.
I don't want to see you tomorrow.
-What?
-But we fly out Tuesday.
I have work,
and then I have a dinner thing,
and then I am busy
trying to become who I am.
Alarm.
What?
-Where is it?
-I don't know.
Miss? You are here.
Already?
Good morning, Charlie.
Why didn't you wake me up?
I didn't mean to sleep with Hannah.
Because you two looked so angelic.
Victoria's secret angel, fat baby angel.
-Don't say that.
-No way, you look awesome these days.
Please avert your eyes.
Is that a present?
Is that for me?
-Give it here.
-Thank you.
You guys fell asleep
to Mary Tyler Moore again, huh?
Yes, guilty.
It's a very odd show
to hear through a wall.
Coming at ya.
Here it comes.
Pow!
I just blew up a kiss on you.
-Are you going to leave your towel on?
-Yes.
But I never see you naked,
and you always see me naked.
When it should actually
be the other way around.
-You are beautiful, shut up.
-I don't need that.
-I need to see your boobs.
-Well, you don't get to, sorry.
I only show my boobs
to people I'm having sex with.
You literally slept
in my bed to avoid him.
I know.
Hannah, I’ve turned a corner.
His touch now feels like
a weird uncle just putting
his hand on my knee at Thanksgiving.
What are you going to do?
-I think I have to end it.
-You can't do that.
I have to. Why not?
'Cause he'll stand
outside our window with a boom box
-or he'll kill himself.
-Stop.
Hey, babe.
Sorry. I thought it was
just my girlfriend in here.
Dude, it's never just
your girlfriend in here.
I'm just saying goodbye.
I'll see you ladies tonight,
and I'll pick up wine.
Okay, big kisses.
Bye.
What does it even feel like
to be loved that much?
I don't know. I can't feel it anymore.
Oh, no.
I know, I just...
And it makes me feel like such a bitch
'cause I can feel him being so nice to me.
And yet it makes me so angry.
I think you need to
admit something to yourself,
which is that you're sick
of eating him out.
'Cause he has a vagina.
-Hi. Ca va?
-Bonjour, roomie.
Oh, my god. You're so hip, I could puke.
I can never pull off that hat.
How do you pull off that hat?
I love your jumper.
Your skin is, like, hauntingly beautiful.
-Can I put my bags down?
-What?
Oh, my god, of course.
You're like my favorite cousin.
I'm the only one of my girlfriends
that has a British cousin.
Well, how long do you think
you're going to stay for?
I mean, not that I'm asking you to leave.
You can totally stay forever
if you want to.
-Can I have something to eat?
-Yeah.
You've been interning there for a year.
You need to tell them
it's time to get paid.
Costs a lot of money to look this cheap.
This is not a joke. If you can't
afford to pay your half of the rent,
Charlie is going to move in here.
-You're dumping Charlie.
-I didn't say that.
So I texted Adam about tonight,
and I have not heard anything back.
Hannah, look at me.
He never, ever texts you back.
Maybe I should call him.
I mean, didn't you say texting's like
the lowest form of communication
-on the pillar of chat?
-The totem of chat,
and no, the lowest,
that would be Facebook,
followed by gChat, then texting,
-then email, then phone.
-Got you.
Face-to-face is, of course, ideal.
But it's not of this time.
Okay, but then how am I
supposed to get him face-to-face
if he refuses to text me?
Think Jessa will really appreciate
the welcome-home dinner.
It's a very friendish thing of us to do.
What?
I just know she's going to show up late,
wearing some fabulous blankety dress
from a Grecian marketplace and be like,
"Oh, I can't remember where I got this."
I'm really glad that she's coming home.
But every time she comes into town,
you go on some week-long bender,
and then she leaves
to go off to her next country
and I'm left to pick up the pieces.
Okay, it is so rare that I say this,
but I just think she's fun.
Yeah, it was really fun
when she fucked Carolyn’s boyfriend.
She didn't fuck your boyfriend.
That's 'cause he was
in Prague that semester.
Thanks so much.
It's a great deal for Nolita.
I mean 2,100 a month? Amaze.
It's a little more expensive
than the dorms,
but Aunt Ilene thinks
it's like the perfect bachelorette pad.
I mean...
Do you like the poster?
Oh, you know, I've never seen that movie.
-Only the show?
-Is it a show?
Oh, my god. You're not serious.
I mean, that's like not being on Facebook.
-I'm not on Facebook.
-You're so fucking classy.
You know, you're funny
because you're definitely like a Carrie
but with, like, some Samantha aspects
and Charlotte hair.
-That's like a really good combination.
-Oh, thank you.
I think I'm definitely a Carrie at heart,
but, like, sometimes...
sometimes Samantha kind of comes out.
And then, I mean, when I’m a school,
I definitely try
and put on my Miranda hat.
Where were you before France?
Before France, I was in Amsterdam...
No, I was in Bali,
and I was shucking pearls there.
And then I met a surfer--
Oh, my god. Did he really like you?
-He really liked you, right?
-Yeah, he really liked me.
-Hannah?
-Hello, Alistair.
Hello.
You seem eager.
As you know,
I've been working here for over a year.
Has it been that long?
Well, you are an invaluable part
of our operation.
Which I recently learned
means very valuable
as opposed to not at all valuable.
And I wanted to let you know
that my circumstances have changed
and I can no longer afford
to work for free.
Oh, Hannah.
I am so sorry to lose you.
I was just going to
start you manning our Twitter,
you have just the quippy voice for that.
Oh, no, I'm not quitting.
I just... I know that Joy-Lynn
got hired after interning,
-so I thought that maybe--
- Hannah.
Joy-Lynn knows Photoshop.
Now, in this economy,
do you know how many
internship requests I get every day?
-I would assume a lot.
-Fifty, it's about fifty.
I practically route them
into my spam folders.
So, if you think you have
just nothing left to learn from us...
No, it is not that, really.
I just, you know, got to eat.
Well, when you get hungry enough,
you're going to figure it out.
Do you mean like
physically hungry or hungry for the job?
I am really going to miss your energy.
I think this is going to be
really good for you.
You mentioned that
when I was finished with my book,
I could send it to you.
Well, we wouldn't have you here
to read it for us. Would we?
Where are you going?
Will you get me a Luna Bar?
And a Smart water and Vitamin water?
Yo, hey.
Yeah, no, I'm actually
just leaving a friend's house
that's, like, right by your house, so...
Yeah?
-Hey, doll.
-Hey.
"Doll," that is what my dad calls me.
Yeah, I know. He told me.
We're in the same circle jerk.
-I just had the worst ever day.
-You were nearby?
Why?
I got fired from my job, so...
Weren't you an intern?
Well, I was working there for a while
-so I was technically an intern.
-So basically,
they just asked you
to not hang out there anymore?
When I was walking over here--
Funny. I was on my way
over here and I was panicking,
but then it occurred to me,
like, I'm an English major,
-there has to be some kind of--
- Major doesn't matter.
I was comp lit and it hasn't done shit.
Yeah, but you're an actor, so aren't you
always comparing different literature?
I don't know.
Plus, I'm into this woodworking stuff.
It's just more honest.
Yeah, it all looks awesome.
But what about your play?
Yeah, we're not doing it.
That guy's a dick.
Can I sit down?
Yeah.
So, if I tell you something,
will you promise that you won't judge me?
Yes.
'Til yesterday, I got all
of my money from my parents.
Okay.
Does that make you feel sick?
Make you not want to talk to me?
No, I mean I wouldn't take shit
from my parents. They're buffoons.
But my grandma gives me
800 dollars a month.
So is, like, that
how you support yourself or...
Yeah. I mean, I supplement.
But it gives me the freedom
that I don't have to be anyone's slave.
You should never be
anyone's fucking slave.
Except mine.
You're feeling pretty frisky.
I really despise that word.
I hate it so much.
I like you so much.
I don't know where you disappear to.
What are you talking about?
I'm right here.
It's so funny that it's still light out,
but it's getting dark
a lot earlier these days.
-Is this some of your poetry?
-Don't be a jerk.
Who, me?
Do you know that part on your resume
where they ask you to list
all of your special skills?
I haven't applied for a job
in a long fucking time.
Okay, well, it's the thing
where they ask you to list, like,
yoga, Spanish, waterskiing, Photoshop.
I feel like I--
don't have any special skills.
-I have something you can do.
-What?
But first, I have to see
if you fulfill all the requirements.
What are the requirements?
Lie on your stomach.
-Now?
-Yes, now. Wait.
You modern career woman,
I know what you like.
You think you can just come in here
and talk all that noise?
Now?
Grab your legs.
-Just... what did you say?
-Grab your legs.
Okay.
Okay, this is good.
-I'm going to go get some lube.
-Why do we need to get lube?
When I get back, I want you
in the exact same position,
but take all the rest of the shit off.
Will you get a condom?
I'll consider it.
Jesus fucking Christ.
This is really hard.
-Is that okay?
-Yeah.
-You putting on a condom?
-No!
-Wait, you are, right?
-Yes.
Okay, 'cause when you said
the thing about lube,
I was worried you were going to try to
do that. Please don't do that.
That feels awful. Thank you.
-It's all right.
-Okay. Thank you.
That's the right spot.
Yeah, sorry.
So I can just stay like this
for a little while?
Yeah.
-Do you need me to move more?
-What?
I just didn't know if you wanted me
to be more like... like that.
Oh, no. This is fine. You're doing great.
This is all you need to do.
I'm sorry about the wrong hole thing.
I just... I don't want to do it now,
and, like, if we did,
I'd just want to talk about it
and just figure out what...
it's just not comfortable for me--
-Let's play the quiet game.
-So you're not mad at me?
No, I'm great.
A great time.
You know what would be crazy?
-What would be crazy?
-Like if we...
just got crazy, right here right now.
We could just do that.
I mean, nobody's stopping us.
Nobody's home.
What would turn you on the most right now?
What would turn me on the most?
What would turn you on the most?
To turn you on,
that's what would turn me on.
-Let me do that.
-Okay.
What if you were a stranger?
-Oh, yeah, a stranger.
-Right? What if...
What if you were just like
a totally different person?
You didn't act like you?
I think Jessa's here.
-Oh, no. I think that might be Ray.
-You invited Ray?
It was going to be
like a four-person party.
That's called dinner.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
What's with all the tattoos?
What do you mean?
Why'd you do all of them?
They're illustrations
from children's books mostly.
Even the one on your ass?
No. That one, my friend Jessa did
sophomore year with a safety pin.
It's a snake wrapped around the moon.
When did you do that?
I did them mostly in high school.
Why?
Truthfully? I gained
a bunch of weight very quickly,
and I just felt
very out of control of my own body,
and it was just like
I had the idea of like,
"I'm taking control of my own shape."
-You know, I was fat in high school.
-Really?
Yeah, but I didn't go
drawing all over myself.
You're not that fat anymore.
You can just have them lasered off.
What time is it?
Five o’clock.
Nine forty five.
I am so late for this dinner thing.
Fuck.
Seriously, this was really, really nice.
It was really good to see you.
I'm glad. Thanks for coming.
It made me feel a lot better, so...
I'll see you soon?
Yeah, just text me.
It's not like they're commandments,
but generally speaking,
as a general rule, I try not to
date women that are under 25
or that have been, at one point
in their life, penetrated by a drummer.
-One time!
-Guilty of both.
But I was walking through
the mall this morning,
I just see these two huge green orbs
bobbing through the mall.
I mean, look at these eyes!
-Have you seen these eyes?
-They're my eyes!
-He's so nice to me.
-Ridiculous.
Look at those lashes, too.
Have you seen these lashes?
-Guilty as charged.
-So cute.
-You okay?
-Yeah.
I just can't believe
Hannah didn't show up.
We're here. Living it up. Partying down.
I didn't mean to be rude.
I'm just not really into eating this week.
Hannah was the one
saying this was our big reunion
and now she's nowhere to be found.
Are you worried?
I mean, should we call someone?
No, especially because
I know exactly where she is.
She's off having gross sex
with that animal.
In what way gross?
Charlie would like to
at least hear about some sex.
Excuse me?
Ray's just being,
you know, like motivational.
I mean, come on, at least you didn't
have to entertain Jessa on her own.
Yeah, 'cause I didn't
get to entertain anybody
because no one came.
-Hannah! Marnie!
-Who's that? She sounds British.
Oh, I ordered a few hookers,
if you guys don't mind.
Bulgarian girls. Top-shelf.
-Nice girls.
-He kills me. I swear to god.
Marnie!
Top lock!
Paris is really where you should be.
If you're a francophile like...
-Me and you, obviously.
-Yeah.
-Then you've got to go to France.
-You have to go.
I was a live-in educator
for these three children,
and they all sang.
And their father
was a brilliant pacifist thinker.
Isn't that the plot to The Sound of Music?
-It is.
-We really want to travel more.
-We could just go.
-Up and go.
I am so sorry I'm so late.
-Hannah banana.
-Would you please come here
-and talk to us?
-Hello.
You're here. You're here. Hi.
What's going on? You look beautiful.
-What'd you say?
-What's going on?
-She smells like sex.
-No, but you showered this morning.
So I calculated,
and I can last in New York
for three and a half more days.
Maybe seven if I don't eat lunch.
I'm going to find you a job
worthy of your talents.
Well, I appreciate that,
but I don't know how you're going to
find a job fast enough.
I'm going to have
to work at, like, McDonald's.
You're not going to work at McDonald's.
What's wrong with McDonald's?
You should work at McDonald's.
It's great. It's fucking incredible.
You know how many people
McDonald's feeds every day?
it employs around the world?
Plus, they make
an incredible product, okay?
It tastes tremendous.
It's affordable. It's fucking consistent.
I can walk into a McDonald's in Nigeria,
order chicken McNuggets.
When I bite into it,
you know what it's going to taste like?
It's going to taste like home.
It doesn't mean I have to work there.
I went to college.
Yeah, I went to college, too.
You know where it left me?
I have 50,000 dollars in student loans.
That's how deep in debt I am.
I'm sorry, but watching this,
this is like watching Clueless.
The movie or the TV show?
-What are you doing?
-What are you doing over there?
I'm making a little brew.
He's making a tea of opium pods.
Oh, cool. So you brought opium
into our apartment.
Well, yeah, this stuff's pretty mild.
This is much milder
than the stuff you'd smoke.
It's legal. I got it down
at the flower district.
You can just go there and buy the pods.
-Is it cool if I have a little?
-Knock yourself out.
-I hate opium.
-Oh, yeah, what's your thing? Coke?
No, I never do coke.
Every time I do coke, I shit my pants.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
-That's horrible.
-It happens.
-What does it taste like?
-It kind of tastes like twigs.
-Yeah, I'll have some.
-Maybe you shouldn't.
You're super sensitive to drugs.
I think I'm going to be fine, okay?
Hand it over.
It's hot.
Oh, Jesus.
This does not taste like Twix.
Not Twix, twigs.
Twigs, like small sticks.
If you're going to vanish,
you have to call, okay?
Yeah, okay. I want to go back in there.
No, you can't.
I need to talk to you first.
All you need to do
is talk to your parents, okay?
You need to ask them to support you
for a little itty-bit longer,
just while you look for another job.
And tell them that
you take your future seriously.
Because you do. You're Hannah.
-Does Charlie have a girlfriend?
-Yes.
Marnie was just saying that she feels
like I need to go and talk to my parents
and ask them to support me
until I get a job.
Why don't you just tell them
that you're an artist?
You just need to tell them
once and for all
-that you are an artist.
-Just tell them
you're going to get a job,
that's much more convincing.
Tell them you'll get tuberculosis
in a garret if you have to.
Tell them it's what Flaubert did.
Flaubert is not a good role model,
and have you met her parents?
She can't just do the artist thing.
Tell them that Picasso did it.
Rappers who were poor
and sold their tapes in the street did it.
It's what Elvis did.
It's what Mick Jagger did.
It's what my stepbrother did.
They all stuck to their guns.
I need to go.
You just drank an entire cup of opium.
You are gorgeous and a vision.
You are a brilliant genius.
Both of you are sex goddesses.
When I look at both of you,
a Coldplay song plays in my heart.
Bye.
God, she seems like
she's in such a good place.
Mom? Papa?
-I think that's Hannah.
-Did she just call me papa?
-Hi!
-Oh, hey.
What the heck are you doing here?
I thought you didn't
want to see us anymore.
Actually, I couldn't bear the idea
of not seeing you before you left town.
But more important...
Here, you can sit down.
It's late. I'm sorry.
is that I brought you my book.
I need you to read it.
Jesus, it's hot.
-Great. Yeah.
-That's fine.
Are you boiling?
Great, we'll read it on the plane.
No, now. I need you to read it now.
Because...
I don't want to freak you out,
but I think that I may be
the voice of my generation.
Or at lease a voice
of a generation.
Well, just read.
Don't be scared, just enjoy it
'cause there's going to be plenty
for us to talk about after.
Just go for it.
I need to talk to you.
All right.
I do not like
what just went down out there. At all.
What, with Hannah?
Yeah, I guess I just don't
understand the problem.
-She seemed ready.
-She had just gotten high.
I'd like for you
to see a real high person.
Marnie, you can't mother her like that.
I'm not mothering her. I'm literally
preventing a disaster from happening.
Have you even read her novel?
It's a memoir, and of course
I've read it, I'm her best friend.
Best friend. This is my best friend.
You know, we don't own anybody.
Maybe you don't respect
what a best friendship means
because you've never stayed
in one place long enough to have one.
Marnie, I can't help your feelings.
Maybe you can help being two hours late
to a dinner party that was thrown for you.
-My god! Yes.
-It was two hours?
-When was dinner?
-Seven!
Seven? I thought
that was just a suggestion.
A suggest... Okay, I'm sorry
we don't eat at one in the morning,
but we don't live in Barcelona.
Maybe not one, but ten, ten’s reasonable.
See, this is what you do.
You act like I'm uptight,
and then I follow suit. I become uptight.
It is the most frustrating dynamic
on the planet.
-It drives me crazy. I can't stand it.
-I'm fucking pregnant.
All right? I'm pregnant.
-On purpose?
-What do you think?
I have to tell you something, you two.
You guys are so beautiful.
Okay, all right.
That's a high person.
-This is very funny stuff, Loreen.
-Yeah.
-Hannah, you're a very funny girl.
-Thank you, papa.
-Okay.
-Oh.
All I am asking for to finish this book
is 1,100 dollars a month
for the next two years.
-That's insane.
-That's a chunk of change.
You would say it's insane.
Who can live in New York
on 1,100 dollars a month?
But I am so committed to this book
that I am willing
to get pretty thrifty on this.
Why don't you get a job and start a blog?
You are so spoiled.
Yeah, well, whose fault is that, Mom?
-Your father's.
-You know this is making me so unhappy.
-I'm having such a horrible feeling.
-Oh, we're not WaMu, Hannah.
And the least you can do
is sit up straight and...
Hannah?
Hannah, Jesus. Hannah?
I shouldn't have taken it,
but I was just having such a bad day.
Taken what? What did you take?
Is she sick, Tad?
Do I need to call a hospital?
I think she may be high.
-It's legal, like flowers.
-Oh, my god.
I'm not going to be angry, Hannah.
All right, I'm just really curious.
-What did you smoke?
-It's opium pods.
It's a tea of opium pods.
-We should Google that.
-I don't need to Google that.
I know about that.
It's tantamount to smoking banana peels.
For Christ's sake,
let's just order her a coffee.
Coffee's for grown-ups.
You're going to drink
a strong cup of coffee!
I'm 24 years old!
Don't tell me what to do.
This is a real display.
No, this is the immediate result
of a cold approach.
You can't just pull the rug out
-from under her so suddenly.
-Why are you doing this?
We should stay a few more days.
Look, I admire your kind heart,
I really do.
But you're getting played
by a major fucking player!
I know! But it's hard
for me to watch her struggle!
My skirt feels so tight.
Maybe you can just cut it
open with a scissors?
It's like watching her get a shot!
-Shots keep people from getting sick!
-Well...
-I want a lake house. I work hard.
-I know.
I want to sit by a fucking lake.
-You deserve a lake.
-I'm going to die
like Flaubert in a garret.
Don't look at me.
Mom?
Dad?
Hi, I'm in room 2507,
and I wanted to get some room service.
But is the account totally closed
if they've checked out?
You can't add anything?
Okay, no. Yeah, got it.
I'm leaving right now. Thank you.
Why don't you smile?
Does your heart hurt?
Oh, girl, when I look at you,
I just want to say,
"Hello, New York!"
Subtitle by Natcha Mabundit